Death comes in twos.
Seconds Apart is a horror, thriller film directed by Antonio Negret.
Seth and Jonah are twins with a dangerous ability: telekinesis.
Things start to spiral out of control as their
classmates die in twisted and bizarre ways.
Jealousy begins to divide them and soon they can no longer trust each
other, leading up to a horrific battle against themselves.
Detective Lampkin, played by Orlando Jones.
Jonah, played by Edmund Entin.
Seth, played by Gary Entin.
Eve, played by Samantha Droke.
Owen Trimble, played by Louis Herthum.
Rita Trimble, played by Morgana Shaw.
Seconds Apart is a 2011 American horror film directed by Antonio Negret
and starring  Orlando Jones, Edmund Entin, and Gary Entin.
The film explores themes of high school, sibling
relationship, hallucination, twin brother, telekinesis.
The tone is intense and dark and mind_bending.